{
    "subject": "resource/Ralph_Hanan",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthYear",
    "object": "1909",
    "human_readable": "Ralph Hanan was born in 1909.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8725705742835999,
            "question": "In what year was Ralph Hanan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7533826231956482,
            "question": "What is the birth year of Ralph Hanan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6874035596847534,
            "question": "What year marks Ralph Hanan's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6451143622398376,
            "question": "Were any famous people born in the same year as Ralph Hanan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5811731815338135,
            "question": "What significant event happened in the year of Ralph Hanan's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48261380195617676,
            "question": "How old was Ralph Hanan in 1929?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48133575916290283,
            "question": "What is known about Ralph Hanan's life after his birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38470491766929626,
            "question": "If today is 2023, how old would Ralph Hanan be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3600831925868988,
            "question": "When did Ralph Hanan come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34104493260383606,
            "question": "What historical events took place during Ralph Hanan's lifetime?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ralph Hanan was born in 1909.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1761_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Ralph Hanan come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1761_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If today is 2023, how old would Ralph Hanan be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1761_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Ralph Hanan's life after his birth year?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1761_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1761_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1761_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1761_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1761_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1761_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1761_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1761_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1761_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1761_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1761_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's my evaluation of whether the triple \"Ralph Hanan was born in 1909\" is correct or not:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1761/re-ranker-msmarco/36.txt, it is mentioned that Ralph Hanan was born on the 13th of June 1909.\n* Similarly, in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1761/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1761/re-ranker-msmarco/29.txt, it is also mentioned that Josiah Ralph Hanan (also known as Ralph Hanan) was born on the 13th of June 1909.\n* Therefore, based on this information, the statement \"Ralph Hanan was born in 1909\" is correct."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Josiah Ralph Hanan, known as Ralph Hanan, was born on June 13, 1909. This supports the statement that Ralph Hanan was born in 1909."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}